Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 April 04; UP056.001.008.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.70 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 April 11; UP056.001.008.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 May 02; UP056.001.008.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.76 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 May 09; UP056.001.008.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.74 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 May 16; UP056.001.008.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.24 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 May 23; UP056.001.008.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.17 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copies in the Reading Room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 May 30; UP056.001.008.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.30 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 June 20; UP056.001.008.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.69 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 October 10; UP056.001.009.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.10 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 October 17; UP056.001.009.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] Graduates in every state
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 October 24; UP056.001.009.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 October 31; UP056.001.009.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 November 07; UP056.001.009.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 November 14; UP056.001.009.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.92 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 November 21; UP056.001.009.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.96 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1,3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 November 28; UP056.001.009.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.56 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1,6.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 December 05; UP056.001.009.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.81 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1917 December 12; UP056.001.009.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.40 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 January 09; UP056.001.009.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.94 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 January 16; UP056.001.009.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 January 23; UP056.001.009.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.88 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 January 30; UP056.001.009.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.50 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 February 06; UP056.001.009.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 February 13; UP056.001.009.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.45 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 February 20; UP056.001.009.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 February 27; UP056.001.009.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.02 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 March 06; UP056.001.009.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 March 13; UP056.001.009.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.11 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni trustees
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 March 20; UP056.001.009.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 March 27; UP056.001.009.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.74 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 April 03; UP056.001.009.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 April 10; UP056.001.009.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.14 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 April 17; UP056.001.009.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.40 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 April 24; UP056.001.009.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.93 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 May 01; UP056.001.009.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.63 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 May 08; UP056.001.009.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.36 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 May 15; UP056.001.009.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.39 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 May 22; UP056.001.009.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 May 29; UP056.001.009.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.94 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 June 12; UP056.001.009.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.21 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 October 23; UP056.001.010.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.74 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 October 30; UP056.001.010.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.57 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. The Tuftonian Vol. 2, no. 1- 1871-1877 Tufts College, MA All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 November 06; UP056.001.010.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.87 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 November 13; UP056.001.010.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.78 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 November 20; UP056.001.010.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.68 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 November 27; UP056.001.010.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.98 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 December 04; UP056.001.010.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.63 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1918 December 11; UP056.001.010.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.54 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alumni association A.W. Coolidge [A1903] appointed secretary
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 January 01; UP056.001.010.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.87 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club; [Alumni association] Executive committee
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 January 08; UP056.001.010.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.25 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 January 15; UP056.001.010.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.40 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 January 22; UP056.001.010.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.46 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 January 29; UP056.001.010.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.85 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 February 05; UP056.001.010.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.26 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Death of (1/31/19) Windom A. Allen (1915) in service (Hero Sons of Tufts) (Makes 16th gold star for Tufts).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 February 12; UP056.001.010.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 February 19; UP056.001.010.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.23 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 February 26; UP056.001.010.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.99 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 March 05; UP056.001.010.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 March 12; UP056.001.010.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 March 19; UP056.001.010.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.18 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 April 02; UP056.001.010.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.60 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 April 09; UP056.001.010.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.90 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 April 16; UP056.001.010.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.11 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alumni trustees
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 April 23; UP056.001.010.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.71 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 April 30; UP056.001.010.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.49 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 May 07; UP056.001.010.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.81 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Death of (10/15/18) Philip Algar (D 1919) in service (Hero Sons of Tufts).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 May 14; UP056.001.010.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.08 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 May 21; UP056.001.010.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.43 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 May 28; UP056.001.010.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 June 04; UP056.001.010.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.97 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 June 11; UP056.001.010.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.94 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 June 25; UP056.001.010.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.36 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 October 01; UP056.001.011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.33 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 October 08; UP056.001.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.79 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 October 15; UP056.001.011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club; [Alumni] E.D. Sabine [A1896] what the alumni do to aid the hill
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 October 22; UP056.001.011.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.26 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 October 29; UP056.001.011.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 November 05; UP056.001.011.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.39 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 November 12; UP056.001.011.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.17 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 November 19; UP056.001.011.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.62 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913-1920. pp. 1,6.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 November 26; UP056.001.011.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.13 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] erecting new plant, p 4
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 December 03; UP056.001.011.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.20 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 December 10; UP056.001.011.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.74 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1919 December 17; UP056.001.011.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.06 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 January 07; UP056.001.011.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 January 14; UP056.001.011.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.20 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 January 21; UP056.001.011.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.45 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 January 28; UP056.001.011.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.60 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 February 11; UP056.001.011.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.59 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 February 18; UP056.001.011.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.62 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 February 25; UP056.001.011.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega; [Alumni] E.D. Sabine [A1896] what the alumni do to aid the hill
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 March 03; UP056.001.011.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 March 10; UP056.001.011.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 March 17; UP056.001.011.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.21 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 March 24; UP056.001.011.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.46 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 March 31; UP056.001.011.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.52 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 April 07; UP056.001.011.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.41 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 April 28; UP056.001.011.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.34 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 May 05; UP056.001.011.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.78 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 May 12; UP056.001.011.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.95 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 May 19; UP056.001.011.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.57 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 May 26; UP056.001.011.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.59 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 June 02; UP056.001.011.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 June 23; UP056.001.011.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.50 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Commencement Issue; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 September 29; UP056.001.012.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.90 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 October 06; UP056.001.012.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.34 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 October 13; UP056.001.012.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.68 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 October 20; UP056.001.012.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.81 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 October 27; UP056.001.012.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 November 03; UP056.001.012.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.17 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] to form cheering section for Detroit game
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 November 10; UP056.001.012.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.74 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 November 17; UP056.001.012.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.09 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1913-1920, pp. 1,4.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 November 24; UP056.001.012.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.14 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 December 01; UP056.001.012.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 December 08; UP056.001.012.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.67 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1920 December 15; UP056.001.012.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 January 12; UP056.001.012.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 January 19; UP056.001.012.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.26 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] Four Tufts men in Massachusetts State Legislature
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 January 26; UP056.001.012.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.45 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 February 09; UP056.001.012.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.15 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 February 16; UP056.001.012.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.56 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 February 23; UP056.001.012.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.99 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 March 02; UP056.001.012.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.64 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 March 09; UP056.001.012.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 March 16; UP056.001.012.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 March 23; UP056.001.012.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.52 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 March 30; UP056.001.012.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.37 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 April 06; UP056.001.012.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.97 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 April 27; UP056.001.012.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.25 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 May 04; UP056.001.012.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.51 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta; [Alumni] Golf Tournament, p3
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 May 11; UP056.001.012.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.18 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 May 18; UP056.001.012.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 May 25; UP056.001.012.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.33 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 June 01; UP056.001.012.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.72 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 June 08; UP056.001.012.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 June 22; UP056.001.012.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.84 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 September 28; UP056.001.013.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.35 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 October 05; UP056.001.013.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.68 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 October 12; UP056.001.013.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club; American association of engineers [Tufts college association of engineers]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 October 19; UP056.001.013.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 October 26; UP056.001.013.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 November 02; UP056.001.013.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.10 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 November 09; UP056.001.013.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.67 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 November 16; UP056.001.013.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.78 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1921-1932, pp. 1,8. Alpha Tau Omega. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 November 23; UP056.001.013.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.19 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 November 30; UP056.001.013.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.24 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 December 07; UP056.001.013.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.61 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1921 December 14; UP056.001.013.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.33 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 January 11; UP056.001.013.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 January 25; UP056.001.013.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.52 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 January 25; UP056.001.013.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.14 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 February 08; UP056.001.013.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.34 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 February 15; UP056.001.013.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.68 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 February 22; UP056.001.013.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.96 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 March 01; UP056.001.013.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.28 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 March 08; UP056.001.013.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.76 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 March 15; UP056.001.013.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.82 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 March 22; UP056.001.013.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 March 29; UP056.001.013.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.38 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 April 05; UP056.001.013.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.96 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 April 26; UP056.001.013.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.36 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 May 03; UP056.001.013.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.45 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 May 10; UP056.001.013.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.99 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 May 17; UP056.001.013.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.22 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 May 24; UP056.001.013.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.41 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. C.A. Adams resigned as professor of mechanical engineering. p. 7 All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 May 31; UP056.001.013.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.43 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 June 07; UP056.001.013.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.09 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 June 19; UP056.001.013.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.71 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Commencement Issue; Alumni day photos, pp 80-81
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 September 27; UP056.001.014.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.25 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Admissions, 1922-23] Entrance Requirements.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 October 04; UP056.001.014.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.31 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 October 11; UP056.001.014.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.53 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 October 18; UP056.001.014.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.83 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 October 25; UP056.001.014.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.46 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 November 01; UP056.001.014.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 November 08; UP056.001.014.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.80 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 November 15; UP056.001.014.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.92 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 November 22; UP056.001.014.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.93 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1921-1932, pp. 1,8; John Coleman Adams. Death of, June 22, 1922.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 November 29; UP056.001.014.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.51 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 December 03; UP056.001.014.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.40 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1922 December 13; UP056.001.014.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.31 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 January 10; UP056.001.014.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 January 17; UP056.001.014.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.35 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 January 31; UP056.001.014.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.19 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 February 07; UP056.001.014.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.43 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 February 14; UP056.001.014.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.16 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 February 21; UP056.001.014.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.16 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 February 28; UP056.001.014.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.96 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 March 07; UP056.001.014.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.40 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 March 14; UP056.001.014.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.83 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 March 21; UP056.001.014.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.66 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 March 28; UP056.001.014.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.97 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 April 04; UP056.001.014.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.77 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 April 11; UP056.001.014.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 May 02; UP056.001.014.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.98 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta; [Alumni] Sons and daughters are tendered a dinner by President Cousens
  - Tufts Weekly, 1923 May 09; UP056.001.014.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.81 Megabytes (Box 14)